http://www.your-diabetes.com/privacy-policy.html

HomeGet Your FREE GiftWhat is Diabetes?Cause of DiabetesDiabetes SymptomOther Health IssuesDiabetic RetinopathyDiabetes ControlDiabetes Weight LossDiabetes SuppliesDiabetic Menu PlanCut The CarbsDiabetes RecipesShare Your RecipeGiant Recipe BookYour Favorite RecipesDiabetes StoriesTell Your StoryDiabetes NewsArticles LibraryGet in TouchDiabetes Site UpdatesCheck These Out...Site Link RequestDiabetes News BlogTerms of UsePrivacy PolicyDiabetes Site MapChristmas Recipes
[?]Subscribe To This Site
My Privacy Policy
If you've arrived at this site, your diabetes.com, from a search engine, then I guess you didn't really want to read my 'Privacy Policy'.
I promise the other pages are far more interesting and worth a visit.
Just use the links on the left to explore and enjoy. Here's the official bit...
http://www.your-diabetes.com is committed to protecting
the privacy of my online visitors. I strive to offer my
visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to
provide an interactive and personalized experience. I
may use personally identifiable information (your name,
e-mail address, street address, telephone number)
subject to the terms of this privacy policy. I will
NEVER sell, barter, or rent your email address to
any unauthorized third party. "Period."
I collect information from online visitors who ask to
be on my newsletter mailing list and/or receive
periodic email announcements. Anyone who wishes can
choose to be removed from my mailing list at any time.
All online visitor data collected by www.Your-Diabetes.com
is protected against unauthorized access. I will not
sell, trade, or give your personal information to other
companies or organizations.
How I gather information from users: How I collect and store information depends on the
when you participate in sweepstakes and contests,
message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive
areas of my site.
recognize you and hold information from your visit.
Among other things, the cookie may store your user name
and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that
information each time you visit, or may control the
number of times you encounter a particular
advertisement while visiting my site.
site’s features according to your preferences.
What I do with the information I collect: Like other Web publishers, I collect information to
enhance your visit and deliver more individualized
content and advertising. I respect your privacy and do
not share your information with anyone.
you or allow anyone to identify you individually.
I may use Personally Identifiable Information
collected on www.Your-Diabetes.com
to communicate with
you about your registration and customization preferences;
my Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and
products offered by www.Your-Diabetes.com and other topics
I think you might find of interest.
Personally identifiable information collected by
www.Your-Diabetes.com may also be used for other purposes
including, but not limited to, site administration,
troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions,
administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other
communications with you.
Certain third parties who provide technical support for the
operation of my site (my Web hosting service for example)
may access such information.
I will use your information only as permitted by law. In
addition, from time to time as I continue to develop
my business, I may sell, buy, merge or partner with
other companies or businesses. In such transactions,
user information may be among the transferred assets.
cases.
Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements: www.Your-Diabetes.com expects its partners, advertisers
and affiliates to respect the privacy of my users. Be
aware, however, that third parties, including my
partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content
providers accessible through my site, may have their
own privacy and data collection policies and practices.
For example, during your visit to my site you may link
to, or view as part of a frame on a www.Your-Diabetes.com
page, certain content that is actually created or hosted
by a third party. Also, through www.Your-Diabetes.com you
may be introduced to, or be able to access, information,
party.
any actions or policies of such third parties.
and this policy.
Children’s Privacy I do not knowingly collect personal information from
children under the age of 13. If I learn that I have
personal information on a child under the age of 13, I
will delete that information from my systems.
www.Your-Diabetes.com encourages parents to go online
with their kids.
Here are a few tips to help make a child's online
experience safer:
* Teach kids never to give personal information, unless
supervised by a parent or responsible adult. Includes
name, address, phone, school, clubs they are a member of,
school extra-curricula activities etc.
* Know the sites your kids are visiting and which sites
are appropriate.
* Look for Web site privacy policies. Know how your
child's information is treated.
Check out the FTC's site for more tips on protecting
children's privacy online:
http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens.html
Top: Your Diabetes Privacy Policy
©2006-2017 Carol Ann Bentley All Rights Reserved.
This is an informational site only.
Please check with your own diabetic health team or physician if you have any concerns.
No responsibility for the use of information on this site or any
third-party websites linked to this site can be accepted.
